If you call yourself a Hussaini, then why are you bound by the laws of the system of
falsehood?
Because my brother, Hazrat Yahya A.S. and Hazrat Zakri A.S. were alive in the rule of
the Romans.
That's why they died.
They used to sit in the Temple of Solomon and do the work of Dawah-e-Tauheed in their
time.
They didn't clash with the system of falsehood, nor did they change the system.
They conveyed the message of Tauheed to the people.
So that when I have such strength, then I can clash with the system of falsehood, which
later people clashed with again.
So you have to look at that time.
So the system of falsehood, the system of falsehood that you are understanding, the
immediate meaning of falsehood comes from the establishment or political parties.
This is not the system of falsehood.
The system of falsehood is the sects of centuries.
The system of falsehood is those fathers who divided one Allah, one Prophet, one Qur'an
believer into so many sects.
So there is only one platform in the world that is against them.
We are the ones who are against the system of falsehood.
When the Ummah does not pray, when the Tauheed of the Ummah is not correct, what do you have
to do by giving it the Islamic system?
Will Barelvi stop saying Ya Ali Madad or Ya Sheikh Abdul Qadir Jilani Madad as soon
as he steals and his hands are cut off?
So by implementing the Islamic system, will there be a difference in his belief?
Will he stop being faithful when the hands of Ahl-e-Hadith are cut off for stealing?
And will he become a believer of Maulana Ali?
No.
The purification of the faith is through narratives, doctrines, and the arguments of the Qur'an
and Sunnah.
Nothing happens by changing the system.
My brother, how strong is your army?
If you bring the head of this army and make him a strict Salafi Wahabi, he cannot break
even one court of Pakistan.
They will skin him alive.
The present army chief, there was no propaganda about him that he is a Qadiani.
He got the ticket at night and went to Umrah.
From there, he shared his pictures.
He invited the Maulvis of the neighborhood and held gatherings in his house.
More than this, he kissed the fingers during the assembly meeting so that Barelvi gets
a degree.
And he got it.
Hanif Qureshi Sahab said proudly that when the assembly meeting was taking place, Bajwa
Sahab kissed the fingers.
My friend, if Barelvi is ready to leave Shirk on kissing the fingers, then I will also kiss
the fingers.
Our real problem with you is that we do not object to you.
Our objection is on Deobandis.
Because the book of Fiqh is one of Deobandis and Barelvis.
It is called Futawa Shami.
It is written in the book Durr-e-Mukhtar that we should kiss the fingers on the name of
the Prophet.
So, we definitely object to the Deobandis that you are hitting a stick in Hanifiyat
and you should kiss the fingers.
So, they say that this Deen is not right.
So, sir, how many Deens are not right in Fazal-e-Maal?
How many Deens are not right in Deobandis?