This drama of Ertugrul Ghazi, which has hundreds of episodes,
the person who wrote the drama, ask him himself,
he says that after digging through the entire history,
I found hardly 4 pages on Ertugrul,
that who was he?
And he has made more than 400 episodes.
And in those 400 episodes, thousands of characters,
hundreds of incidents of Samoa have been included.
And the person who wrote it, he says that he found 4 pages.
So ask him that you have made 4 lakh pages.
Not 4000.
Start writing from that episode.
So he says that I have designed it myself,
presented it as a drama.
But the Pakistani people have understood that this is what happened.
That is, this happened with Ertugrul in this way.
Now you will say that I have seen it myself, this was happening.
Our youth who sleep after watching Hollywood movies in millions,
we will tell them to watch the Umar series too.
So that you know what are the real heroes of Islam.
And then the consultants of the Umar series are not stupid scholars.
They are the top of the list scholars in the world.
The rest are just scholars with degrees, they are real researchers.
Who are considered to be non-believers and Muslim authorities.
Number one, Yusuf Al-Qardawi.
He is 90 plus age.
Mufti Azam Qatar, he is his consultant.
His students are Dr. Ali Silabi,
whose Daruslam-e-Hadith has published such thick books.
Dr. Ali Silabi has published the biography of Hazrat Abu Bakr, Umar, Usman, Ali, etc.
He is his student.
He is a consultant.
Mufti Azam is Saudi Arabian, he is not at the level of knowledge.
It is okay if you talk about someone else.
These are the people.
These are the people whose books are taught by Arab scholars.
In Islam, Halal and Haram is the book of Yusuf Al-Qardawi.
Which you can consider as the only recognized book on modern age issues.
In modern age issues, only one book has been written in the world,
that is Halal and Haram in Islam.
It has been translated into Urdu.
And this is taught to the scholars in Saudi Arabia as a textbook.
And this is written by Yusuf Al-Qardawi, who is a consultant of the Umar series.
I am telling you his level of knowledge.
And Yusuf Al-Qardawi has the honor of teaching the funeral of Mullah Muddudi.
There was so much disagreement as to who was going to teach the funeral.
Imam-e-Kaaba was also eager.
Because the first award given to Dr. Zakir Naik in 2015 was given to Mullah Muddudi.
But then there was a consensus that Dr. Zakir Naik, who is no greater than Yusuf Al-Qardawi,
will teach the funeral.
In Qazafi Stadium.
The biggest funeral of Mullah Muddudi in Pakistan's history has been given.
And Yusuf Al-Qardawi taught it.
And he also writes to Mullah Muddudi as Al-Imam and quotes his references.
Now he is 90 plus years old.
So he is that consultant.
Therefore, we say that the children of our Muslims,
who you will give to read Islamic history, no one reads the books.
Our lecturers see the books, but no one reads them.
I say that I have recorded a lecture on the life of the Prophet,
which was recorded in two hours, and there are 500 pages in the book,
but no one will read it.
But this lecture has been seen by millions of people.
So we say that those people,
we do not give you advice, you watch the Umar series.
Those who already watch the films, must watch it.
You also watch it.
So in my opinion, there is no harm in it.
Except that you pay attention to the women's scene.
Otherwise, it is a very less scene.
Most of the scenes are very positive.