Exactly 10 years ago to the day I uploaded my first video on this YouTube channel,
which was a little devlog video about my first ever game project that I'd just started a few
months earlier. A decade later and I'm still making games and devlog videos,
so to celebrate this milestone I want to take you through that 10 year journey,
from that very first game that I made as a hobby in my university dorm room,
to releasing my first commercial game and becoming a full time indie game developer.
To start the story though we need to go back a little further than 10 years, to the end of 2012
where I'd just had the idea for a game that, at the time, I thought was such a good idea
that I needed to learn how to make games just so that I could make that game.
I was 20 years old at the time and I'd just finished my second year at university,
where I was studying computer science, so I knew the basics of programming,
but apart from the coursework they set us I'd never really attempted any big projects before.
So, full of enthusiasm about my new idea for a game, I googled